https://foapom.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Festival of Arts Pageant of the Masters
Skip to content
Where Art Comes to Life!
TICKETS
DONATE
Pageant of the MastersAbout the PageantPageant ThemeBehind-the-ScenesVolunteerCelebrity BenefitRaffle2020 Cancellation InformationTicketsSingle TicketsGroup SalesMasters at GivingTicket PoliciesMade in AmericaIn the 2021 Pageant of the Masters, audiences will meet the artists who made this country their home and were inspired by the freedoms upon which this nation was founded.
Festival Art ShowAbout the Art ShowArtist GalleryArt Tours, Demos & ExhibitsArt Workshops/ClassesBecome an ExhibitorEvents & MusicCelebrity BenefitRaffleAdmissionMeet our ArtistsOver 100 juried artists from Orange County exhibit their original fine art at the Festival Art Show.
foaVirtual Online GalleryExplore the artwork of Festival exhibitors from the comfort of your home in 3D galleries.
Plan Your VisitPlan Your VisitAttending the EventDirections/ParkingDining/HotelsAccessibilityFAQsHouse RulesFirst Time Visitor?What to expect, what to bring and other helpful hints.
Grab a Bite!Discover dining options at the Festival.
Join & SupportJoin & SupportMembershipDonateIndividual GivingMasters at GivingSponsorshipOpportunitiesJob OpeningsPageant VolunteerFestival VolunteerBecome an ExhibitorWe need your help!Find out how you can support the Festival and Pageant during these challenging times.
About UsABOUT USBoard of DirectorsHistoryFacility RentalsGrants/ScholarshipsPermanent Art CollectionFOA at HomeOff-Site ExhibitsNews/UpdatesSponsorsContactGrants & ScholarshipsFind out more about applying for our foundation grants and scholarship programs.
FOA at HomeDiscover digital art programs and resources that you can enjoy from the comfort of home.
CalendarShop
Search for:
Pageant of the MastersTicketsAbout the PageantVolunteerCelebrity Benefit EventFestival Art ShowVirtual Art ExhibitAbout the Art ShowMeet our ArtistsEvents & MusicArt Workshops & ClassesGrounds MapArt Tours, Demos & ExhibitsBecome an ExhibitorAdmissionPlan Your VisitAttending the EventDirections & ParkingDining & HotelsAccessibilityHouse RulesFAQsJoin & SupportDonateMembershipSponsorshipOpportunitiesAbout UsNewsFacility RenovationsHistoryGrants & ScholarshipsPermanent Art CollectionfoaTVOff-Site ExhibitsSponsorsBoard of DirectorsContactCalendarOnline Store
Privacy Policy
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policymperez2020-02-19T09:24:12-08:00
The Festival of Arts respects your right to privacy and your requirements to control personal information. “Personal information” includes, but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card information. The Festival of Arts does not sell any personal information.
The intent of this Privacy Statement is to inform users of our internet sites, including foapom.com and http://ev3.evenue.net/cgi-bin/ncommerce3/EVExecMacro?linkID=foa&evm=main on how the sites collect, store, and use personal information submitted via the site.
Collection of Information
No software or hardware techniques are employed to capture a visitor’s e-mail address without their knowledge. Certain applications on our websites may require users to register or to provide personal information in order to make a commerce transaction, to enter a contest, or to subscribe to a newsletter. To better enable us to service our patrons, the websites may be used as a survey tool to request demographic information. Entry of such information is optional and if you choose not to enter such information, you can successfully use these applications. If we request demographic information, we will not share your personal information as an individual with any other entity. If we do share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.
Mailing Lists
If you provide your e-mail address, the Festival of Arts may contact you periodically with special offers, updated information and new services. Any e-mails sent to you by the Festival of Arts offer you the option to be removed from the e-mail mailing list.
Selected applications on our web site allow visitors to subscribe to our email newsletter by providing their name and email address. If you provide the Festival of Arts with your email, mailing address or telephone number, the Festival of Arts may use this information to alert you to updated information and new services. If you wish to be removed from these mailing lists, you may unsubscribe at any time by clicking the “modify subscriptions” link in the email you received or by contacting the Festival of Arts directly. (See the ‘Contact Us’ section below).
Information to Third Parties
The Festival of Arts may occasionally present a special contest or promotion on its website that is sponsored by another company. To qualify for entry, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share that information with the sponsor(s), we will provide a statement to that effect.
Security Used
The Festival of Arts stores all user information in secure databases protected via a variety of access controls. Access controls include: password protection, electronic firewalls and data encryption. SSL encryption is used to protect all personal and financial information, and credit card information is not stored on a Web-enabled server. This data is accessed only for purposes specified in this privacy policy.
Financial Information
The Festival of Arts will protect any personal financial information that you share with us. If you make a purchase on-line, we will use your credit card number only to process your payment and will not use it for marketing purposes. For reasons of security, credit card information is not stored on our Web Server. We will retain order information for our records, but this information is never shared with third parties.
Links
Our sites include links to other websites whose privacy policies we do not control. Once you leave our servers (you can confirm where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you cannot find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site’s homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information. The Festival of Arts is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Cookies
Certain applications on Festival of Arts websites invoke a standard feature found in browser software called a “cookie.” We use cookies to track the progress of e-commerce transactions and to allow site users to move from one page to the next without having to re-enter personal order information. We do not share information transferred through cookies with third parties.
Children
We do not solicit personal information from children. Sites specifically geared toward children will not request any personal or contact information.
Contact Us/ How to Update Your Personal Information
You can maintain the accuracy of your personal information by notifying us when you change your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from the Festival of Arts, our partners, or selected third parties, e-mail tickets@LagunaPageant.com: or call 800-487-3378; or or by postal mail at:
Festival of Arts, 650 Laguna Canyon Road, Laguna Beach, CA 92651
Please include your old and new contact information so that we can make the appropriate corrections. The Festival of Arts would like to receive your comments and any questions about this policy. Please address comments or questions regarding the Festival of Arts privacy practices to the addresses listed above. The Festival of Arts may occasionally update this policy. Notice of revisions will be posted here.
Disclaimer
Under no circumstances shall the Festival of Arts, its employees, or its contractors be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive or consequential damages that may result in any way from your use or inability to use the information provided on this or any other web site supported or maintained by the Festival of Arts, or from your reliance on or use of information, services or merchandise provided on or through the web site or that result from mistakes, errors, omissions, interruptions, defects, deletion of files, delays in operation or transmission or any failure of performance. If you are dissatisfied with the information provided on this web site, or with any of the practices of the Festival of Arts in the operation of this web site, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the web site.
TERMS OF USE:
By using this site and/or providing us with personal information, you agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Festival of Arts, its officers, trustees, directors, employees, successors, agents, distributors and affiliates for any and all claims, damages, losses, fees and causes of action arising from its use by you or any information or content provided by you.
The information provided on this site is for general use by its audience and all programs and artists are subject to changes without notice. Information contained on this site is presented “as is” and may contain inaccuracies and omissions. Any and all information presented on this website is done so without warranty, either expressed or implied, and any reliance on the information contained herein will be made at your own risk.
Copyright/Ownership
This website is owned, operated and maintained by the Festival of Arts. Unless otherwise specified, all information and content of this site, including text, logos, graphics, and images are the sole property of the Festival of Arts and may not be reproduced or used without our permission.
About Us
The Laguna Beach Festival of Arts is a 501c3 with a mission to promote, produce, and sponsor events and activities that encourage the appreciation, study and performance of the arts. Throughout each year the Festival of Arts sponsors art education programming, art exhibits and provides art scholarships to local high school students as well as grants for local non-profit art organizations through its Foundation.
Read more
NavigationPageant of the Masters
Festival Art Show
Plan Your Visit
Join & Support
About Us
Shop
Mailing List Signup
©2020 Festival of Arts. All Right Reserved.
|   Privacy Policy   |   Website Design by Web Casa
FacebookTwitterInstagram
